import { Set } from "../interfaces/sets.interface";

const allSets = [
  {
    set: {
      id: 9,
      name: "Grammar - Beginner 1",
      createdDateTime: "1702236644185",
      updatedDateTime: "1703163038729",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 50,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "안녕하세요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Hello. \n\n안녕 = well-being, peace, health. \n하세요 = you do, do you?, please do. \n",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 51,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "감사합니다",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Thank you. \n\n감사 = appreciation, thankfulness, gratitude. \n합니다 = I do, I am doing. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 52,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "네",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "I agree. Affirmative. Yes? Uh huh. Yeah. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 53,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "아니요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "No. I disagree. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 54,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "맞아요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'Can be used after 네 to say "Yes, you are right". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 55,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "안녕히 계세요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Stay in peace (Goodbye)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 56,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 6,
        front: "안녕히 가세요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Go in peace (Goodbye)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 57,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 7,
        front: "죄송합니다",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "I apologize (chweh-song hamnida)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 58,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 8,
        front: "저기요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "(excuse me) Hey you, 'over there!' - politely",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 59,
        deckId: 9,
        ordinal: 9,
        front: "잠시만요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Just a second (passing through crowd bumping into people)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 10,
      name: "Grammar - Beginner 2",
      createdDateTime: "1703163055956",
      updatedDateTime: "1703163055956",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 63,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "이거 (in 이거 뭐예요)",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'This - "what is THIS?" Also 이거 물이에요 - "This is water"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 64,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "뭐 in 뭐예요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "What? As in what is it?",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 65,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "이에요 and 예요",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"it is" or "is it"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 66,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "이",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "This (near you)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 67,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "저",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "That (over there)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 68,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "그",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "The / that (near the other person)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 69,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 6,
        front: "아니에요 ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "To be not (polite, present tense). Can also be said in response to 'thank you'. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 70,
        deckId: 10,
        ordinal: 7,
        front: "은/는",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Marks the topic of the sentence, and puts emphasis on it. 이 책은 = This book (topic of this sentence)",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 1,
      name: "Hangeul Level 1",
      createdDateTime: "1698293938968",
      updatedDateTime: "1702236486807",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 1,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "What sound does 으 make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'Neutral (unhappy face) sound, "eu". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "What sound does 오 make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'The "o" sound from "old". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "What sound does 우 make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Ooh"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "What sound does 이 make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"ee"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "What sound does 어 make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"uh", or eo',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "What sound does 아 make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"ah"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 45,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 6,
        front: "What does ㅇ do?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Place holder consonant, makes no sound. Turns a vowel into a full character by being a pair. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 46,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 7,
        front: "What does ㅣ represent? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Human beings",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 47,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 8,
        front: "What does . represent?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Sky",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 48,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 9,
        front: "What does ㅡ represent?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Ground",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 49,
        deckId: 1,
        ordinal: 10,
        front: "How do you Koreanize English words?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Add ㅡ to the end. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 3,
      name: "Hangeul Level 2",
      createdDateTime: "1698800415541",
      updatedDateTime: "1702195289848",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 12,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "What sound does ㄱ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"G" or "K", a "clicky" G. \nPush your tongue forward slightly more forward than an English G would normally require. ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "What sound does ㅋ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅋ = "K".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "What sound does ㄴ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"N" sound - Tongue bottom of upper teeth. It\'s a "soft N". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "What sound does ㄷ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "ㄷ = D/Th (keep tongue on top lower teeth).",
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "What sound does ㄹ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'A rolling "R". Can resemble the "L" sound in the middle of a word. ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 17,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "What sound does ㅁ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"M"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 18,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 6,
        front: "What sound does ㅂ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅂ = Soft "B".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 23,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 7,
        front: "What sound does ㄲ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㄲ = "G".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 24,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 8,
        front: "What sound does ㄸ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㄸ = "D". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 25,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 9,
        front: "What sound does ㅌ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅌ = "T".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 26,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 10,
        front: "What sound does ㅍ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅍ = "P".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 27,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 11,
        front: "What sound does ㅃ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅃ = "B".',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 44,
        deckId: 3,
        ordinal: 12,
        front:
          "What happens to the sound of a consonant when you add lines to it?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Two things:\n- More friction in the sound.\n- Higher pitch! ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 5,
      name: "Hangeul Level 3",
      createdDateTime: "1699412859336",
      updatedDateTime: "1702236493025",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 20,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "What sound does ㅅ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"S" (soft)',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 21,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "What sound does ㅈ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅈ = between "ch" and "j", light.',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 22,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "What does ㅎ do when in a syllable block?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'More friction when you let air through your mouth, like an "H". \n\n오 = eo. \n호 = heo (like o in old). ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 28,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "What sound does ㅊ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅊ= added friction and air to ㅈ (between "j" and "ch"). ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 29,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "What sound does ㅆ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅆ = "S" (less air escape). ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 30,
        deckId: 5,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "What sound does ㅉ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'ㅉ = added friction to (ㅈ) like "t". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 6,
      name: "Hangeul Level 4",
      createdDateTime: "1701992373658",
      updatedDateTime: "1702236496656",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 31,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "What sound does ㅘ make? ",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Wah". ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 32,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "What sound does ㅝ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Wuh"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 33,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 2,
        front: "What sound doesㅐmake?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'Ai without a mouth change, like "eh"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 34,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 3,
        front: "What sound doesㅔmake?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'Ai, or "eh" much like ㅐ(which is more open). ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 35,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 4,
        front: "What sound does ㅞ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Weh", but with a hint of "ai"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 36,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 5,
        front: "What sound does ㅚ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Weh" with an "ai" sound',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 37,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 6,
        front: "What sound does ㅙ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"Weh", but with a hint of "ai"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 38,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 7,
        front: "What sound does ㅟ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"We"',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 39,
        deckId: 6,
        ordinal: 8,
        front: "What sound does ㅢ make?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "This is phonetic, say as seen. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 7,
      name: "Hangeul Level 5",
      createdDateTime: "1702015740779",
      updatedDateTime: "1702236501397",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 40,
        deckId: 7,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: 'How does "Y" work in Hangeul?',
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: 'You can take the following vowels:\nㅏ,ㅓ,ㅗ,ㅜ,ㅐ,ㅔ. \n\nAnd add a line to them:\nㅑ,ㅕ,ㅛ,ㅠ,ㅒ,ㅖ. \n\nWhich adds a "y" sound to the beginning. ㅏ(Ah) would become ㅑ(Yah). \n\n',
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    set: {
      id: 8,
      name: "Hangeul Level 6",
      createdDateTime: "1702189735918",
      updatedDateTime: "1702236505013",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        id: 41,
        deckId: 8,
        ordinal: 0,
        front: "What sound does ㅇ make at the end of a block?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: '"ng" like sting and ring. ',
        answerImage: "",
      },
      {
        id: 42,
        deckId: 8,
        ordinal: 1,
        front: "How do you handle a consonant at the end of a word?",
        questionImage: "",
        questionVoice: "",
        back: "Short stop. Most consonants are said normally at the end, but some are reduced to a simple form. These rules will be covered more in depth in the pronunciation course. ",
        answerImage: "",
      },
    ],
  },
];

const newSets: Set[] = allSets.map((item) => {
  return {
    id: item.set.id,
    name: item.set.name,
    description: "",
    cards: item.cards.map((x) => {
      return {
        front: x.front,
        back: x.back,
        extra: "",
      };
    }),
  };
});

console.log(newSets);
